I’m a little confused when I think of you
思い浮ぶあなたのことで
떠올린 네 생각에
当我想起你时
頭がいっぱい
머리가 좀 복잡해
我有点困惑
I feel like my head is going to crack
頭が複雑
깨질 것만 같아
感觉头要炸了
Full of fantasy
満ちるＦａｎｔａｓｙ
가득한 Fantasy
充满Fantasy
Curious mystery
気になるＭｙｓｔｅｒｙ
궁금한 Mystery
弥漫Mystery
Please give me a hint
ヒントをお願い
제발 힌트를 줘
请给我提示
I’m following your every little move
細かいことまで真似をする
사소한 것 하나까지 널 따라해
我模仿你的一举一动
ミスじゃない自然とＹｅａｈ
실수한 건 아냐 자연스럽게 Yeah
这可不是失误很自然 Yeah
It’s not a mistake, naturally yeah
I’ve become addicted to your scent that’s
すでに深く染まった君という香りに
이미 몸에 깊게 배인 너란 향기에
我已经沉迷于你的香气
already been deeply permeated through my body
中毒された
중독이 돼 버린 거야
深深地渗透到我的身体
I can’t do anything without you
君がいなければ何もできない
너 없인 난 아무것도 못 해
没有你我什么也做不了
You probably think that I’m a fool yeah
バカのように見られてもＹｅａｈ
내가 바보 같아 보이겠지 Yeah
你可能觉得我是个笨蛋 Yeah
My heart can’t beat without you
君がいなければ心臓も動かない
심장이 너 없인 뛰질 못해
没有你我的心无法跳动
From head to toe
頭から足元まですべて
머리부터 발끝까지 모두
从头到脚
I love you all
全部好きだよ
다 사랑해
爱你的一切
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
An instant spark spreads, flame
ちょっとした火種が広まってＦｌａｍｅ
잠깐의 불씨가 퍼져 Flame
瞬间的火花蔓延Flame
Never get away from my frame
絶対に離れないで僕のＦrａｍｅ
절대로 벗어나지 마 내 Frame
永远不要离开我的Frame
My emotions have inflated 100%
膨れ上がった感情が１００％
부피가 커진 내 감정이 100%
我的情绪已经膨胀100%
Full of you, come on in my arms
君で満ちた胸の中にＣｏｍｅ　ｏｎ　ｉｎ
너로 차올라 내 품에 Come on in
满满的你在我怀里Come on in
Come on in come on in, come to me you
Ｃｏｍｅ　ｏｎ　ｉｎ　ｃｏｍｅ　ｏｎ　ｉｎ僕に君は
Come on in come on in 내게로 넌
Come on in come on in到我这里
Just look at me, like the hot sun
太陽のように僕だけを見て
나만 바라봐 뜨거운 태양처럼
看着我如炙热的阳光
You’re turning me upside down
勝手に僕の心を奪って
맘대로 내 맘을 뒤집어 놓고
你已经让我心慌意乱
Don't turn around! Hold my hand
背を向けないで！手をつないで
돌아서지 마! 내 손을 잡아
别转身！握住我的手
I can't go outside, you're driving me crazy
外に出れない、君のせいでつらい
밖에 못 나가 너 때매 미쳐
我不能出去你让我痴狂
Like a restless beast
もてあますＢｅａｓｔ
주체 못 하는 Beast
像一只不安的Beast
Sing to you under the moonlight
月の下で君に歌う
달빛 아래 네게 노랠 불러
在月光下为你歌唱
Can you hear me, where u at? My boo
聞こえるのＷｈｅｒｅ　ｕ　ａｔ？　Ｍｙ　ｂｏｏ
들리니 Where u at? My boo
听得见吗Where u at? My boo
I can’t do anything without you
君がいなければ何もできない
너 없인 난 아무것도 못 해
没有你我什么也做不了
You probably think that I’m a fool yeah
バカみたいでもＹｅａｈ
내가 바보 같아 보이겠지 Yeah
你可能觉得我是个笨蛋 Yeah
My heart can’t beat without you
君がいなければ心臓も動かない
심장이 너 없인 뛰질 못해
没有你我的心无法跳动
From head to toe
頭から足元まですべて
머리부터 발끝까지 모두
从头到脚
I love you all
全部好きだよ
다 사랑해
爱你的一切
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
Oh my god
Everyday up and down
毎日Ｕｐ　ａｎｄ　ｄｏｗｎ
매일 Up and down
每天Up and down
You are the one who soaked me
ドライな僕を湿したのは君だよ
건조한 날 흠뻑 적신 건 너야
是你让我湿透了
You’re driving me crazy every night
夜ごとに君のせいで
매일 밤 너란 사람 때매
是你每天晚上
狂ってしまう
미쳐 버린 거야
让我痴狂
I failed to control myself
コントロールできない
수위 조절 실패야
我没能控制自己
OH OH OH
I can’t do anything without you
君がいなければ何もできない
너 없인 난 아무것도 못 해
没有你我什么也做不了
You probably think that I’m a fool yeah
バカみたいでもＹｅａｈ
내가 바보 같아 보이겠지 Yeah
你可能觉得我是个笨蛋 Yeah
My heart can’t beat without you
君がいなければ心臓も動かない
심장이 너 없인 뛰질 못해
没有你我的心无法跳动
From head to toe
頭から足元まですべて
머리부터 발끝까지 모두
从头到脚
We goin’ hard hotter and hotter
Ｗｅ　ｇｏｉｎ’　ｈａｒｄもっと熱く
We goin’ hard 더 뜨겁게
We goin’ hard 更火爆
LA LA LA LA LA
We make it pop to burn it
Ｗｅ　ｍａｋｅ　ｉｔ　ｐｏｐ燃やすんだ
We make it pop 불태울게
We make it pop 燃起来
LA LA LA LA LA
Put your hands up In the air Say
Let’s make love Hey
I love you all
全部好きだよ
다 사랑해
爱你的一切
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你
I love you
君が好きだよ
널 사랑해
我爱你